Finding aid for the Hearst Corporation Los Angeles Examiner photographs, negatives and clippings - oversize portrait and subject files 7000.3
USC Libraries Special Collections
Hearst Corporation Los Angeles Examiner photographs, negatives and clippings--oversize portrait and subject files
Bulk, 1930-1959
1903-1961
7000.3
USC Libraries Special Collections
493.12 linear ft. 368 flat storage boxes
This finding aid is for the oversize portrait and subject files of the Los Angeles Examiner photograph morgue.
Hearst Corporation.
Conditions Governing Access
Advance notice required for access.
Arrangement
The photographic morgue of the Hearst newspaper the Los Angeles Examiner consists of the photographic print and negative files maintained by the newspaper from its inception in 1903 until its closing in 1962. It contains approximately 1.4 million prints and negatives. The collection is divided into multiple parts: 7000.1 - Portrait Files; 7000.2 - Subject Files; 7000.3 - Oversize Portrait and Subject Files; 7000.4 - Negatives. Each part of the collection is then divided into 26 series, one for each letter of the alphabet, with the exception of the 7000.3 set, which is divided into 2 series -- Oversize Portrait Files and Oversize Subject Files, and then each series is divided into 26 subseries, one for each letter of the alphabet.
Scope and Content
7000.3--Oversize Portrait and Subject files consist of over 3800 folders of photographic prints. The oversize portrait and subject files are gelatin silver prints and made larger than the conventional American standard of 8x10 inches. Many are as large as 11x17 inches, or maybe smaller but have backing larger than 8x10 inches. The dates of the prints range from the 1930s to the paper's closure in 1961. There are no negatives in this particular collection. Newspaper libraries weeded their morgues from time to time to remove images that were judged to have lost their news value.
If the print was used in the newspaper, it usually bears a pasted-down clipping of the published image with its caption and a stamped date on its back. Most prints include at least the name of the subject and a stamped date indicating when it was deposited in the morgue. While there are photographs taken by Examiner staff photographers scattered throughout the files, most of the prints are publicity photographs or from wire services such as the Associated Press or International News.
The prints in this collection formed the active working files for the editors, writers, and photographers of the newspaper. They were used repeatedly (and some, frequently) over an extended period and show signs of use, including bending, creasing, tearing, marking, and wear-and-tear. Many of the prints show permanent evidence of their use such as crop marks and retouching by highlighting or shading. These marks cannot be removed as they are an integral part of the record of a working newpaper morgue and have been preserved as part of the history of the morgue.
The Oversize Portrait files, contained in over 2500 folders, consist of both formal portraits and snapshots of people. Prominent Californians and Los Angelenos, as well as historical figures from the 1930s to the late 1950s, are represented. The Oversize Portrait files are arranged in the original order in which they were received from the Los Angeles Examiner, which is loosely alphabetical by surname. Many of the files contain alphabetical ranges of surnames, but those people who were better known, whose prints were frequently used, or who had a large quantity of prints, received their own files. However, the range of files and the individual files are not mutually exclusive, and it is recommended that the researcher look in the range even if the person has his or her own file(s). For photographs of women, researchers should look up alternate spellings, pseudonyms, and maiden and married names.
In addition, the Examiner also maintained a separate morgue called the Closet File, which included the famous people, and was not included in the donation to USC.
The Oversize Subject files, contained in over 1300 files, consist of snapshots of events, places, and things. Subjects heavily represented include atomic energy, aviation, baseball, hosrses, and Los Angeles. The subject files are mostly arranged in the alphabetical order in which they were received from the Los Angeles Examiner. Most of the files contain prints related to a specific subject, although there also are files consisting of a range of terms.
In addition to the Subject files, the Examiner also maintained a separate morgue called the Tower, which was not included in the donation to USC.
Historical Note
The Los Angeles Examiner was founded in December 1903 by William Randolph Hearst. A morning paper, it printed its last issue on January 7, 1962. The paper closed at the same time as the Times-Mirror afternoon paper the Los Angeles Mirror. These closures left the Los Angeles Times as the only significant morning newspaper in Los Angeles and the Los Angeles Evening Herald Express, another Hearst paper, as the only significant afternoon paper. After its closure, the Examiner was absorbed by the Herald amp Express, which was renamed the Herald-Examiner. The Examiner was a right-leaning paper and published as a broadsheet. At the time of its closure, the paper had a daily circulation of about 380,000 and a Sunday circulation of about 700,000. The closure of the paper at the same time as that of the Los Angeles Mirror caused the Department of Justice to open an informal restraint-of-trade investigation into possible collusion between the Hearst and Times-Mirror companies.
Hearst Corporation. -- Archives; California, Southern--History--Archival resources; Los Angeles (Calif.)--Newspapers--Archival resources; Newspapers--Archival resources; Photographs
- Oversize Portrait Files
  - A
    - Aa-Abz (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Abbott, Abott, Abot, Abot -- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Ac -- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Acheson, Dean (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Acquanette (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Ad-Ae -- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Adams A-Z (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Adams, Abigail -- Actress (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Adams, Julia - Actress (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Addams, Dawn -- Actress (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Adenauer, Konrad (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Af-Ah -- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Agar, John -- Mr. and Mrs. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Ai-Ak (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Ala -- Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Alb -- Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Alberghetti, Anna Maria (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Albright, Eddie (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Alc-Alh -- Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Aleman, Miguel (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Aleman, Miguel -- U.S.A. Tour Pictures (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Alexander, A-Z -- Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Allan, Elizabeth -- Actress (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Allbritton, Louise -- Actress (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Allen, A-Z -- Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Allyson, June (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Almond, Edward (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Alsop, Carleton (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Ameche, Don -- Actor (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Amsbry, Mickey (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Ana-Aqz (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Anderson, A-L (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Anderson, M-Z -- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Anderson, Richard, Carol Lee Ladd -- Mr. and Mrs. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Andrews -- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Andrews, Dana (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Andrews, Frances -- Mrs. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Angeli, Pier -- Actress (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Ap-Arh (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Arabia Royalty -- Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Aragon, Art -- Boxer (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Arcaro, Eddie (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Arden, Eve -- Actress (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Ari-Aro (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Armour, Norman (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Armstrong, A-Z (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Arnall, Ellis, Governor (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Arnaz, Desi -- And Wife Lucille Ball (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Arnold, A-Z (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Arnold, Edward -- And Wife Cleo (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Arp-Arz (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - As -- Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Ashley, Sylvia, Lady (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Astaire, Fred (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - At -- Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Attlee, Clement, Prime Minister (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Atwood, A-Z (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Atwood, Donna -- Skater (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Au-Auz (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Aubrey, Cecile (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Aumont, Jean Pierre -- Actor (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Auriol, Vincent (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Austin, A-Z (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Avak (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - B
    - Baa-Bad (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Babich (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Bacall, Lauren (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Bae-Baj (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Bailey, A-Z (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Bak-Bal (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Baker, A-Z (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Baker, Beverly -- Tennis (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Ball, Lucille -- Actress (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Ball, Suzan -- Actress (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Bam-Baq (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Bankhead, Tallulah (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Bara-Barl (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Barber, A-Z (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Bari, Lynn -- Actress (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Barker, A-Z (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Barker, Lex -- Actor (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Barkley, Alben -- Alone and Groups of Two, Not With Mrs. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Barkley, Alben -- Large Groups Not With Mrs. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Barkley, Alben -- with Mrs. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Barm-Bars (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Barnes, A-Z (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Barnett, A-Z (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Barret, Barrett, A-Z (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Barry, A-Z (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Barry, Gene (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Barrymore, A-Z (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Barrymore, John -- Jr. and Wife (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Barrymore, Lionel -- Actor (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Bart-Barz (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Bartholomew, Freddie (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Bartlett (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Bartlett, E.L. -- Alaskan Delegate (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Barton, Otis (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Baruch, Bernard (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Bas-Bat (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Basilio, Carmen (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Bates -- Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Bates, Barbara (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Batista, Fulgencio (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Bau-Baz (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Bauer, Marlene (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Bautzer, Greg (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Baxter, Anne -- Actress (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Bea-Beaz (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Beal-Beale (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Beaudry, Emil J., Lieutenant Colonel -- And Family (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Beb-Bed (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Becerra, Jose -- Boxer (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Beck, A-Z (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Becker, A-Z (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Bee-Ber (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Beery, Wallace -- Actor (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Beirne, Joseph A. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Bel Geddes, Barbara (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Bel-Belz (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Belita (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Bell, A-Z (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Bellamy, A-Z (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Belloise, Steve (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Bem-Beq (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Ben-Gurion, David (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Bender, Elmer C. -- Mr. and Mrs. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Bendix, William (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Bennett, A-Z (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Bennett, Constance -- Actress (Box 11, Folder 1 - 2)
    - Bennett, Joan -- Actress (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Benny, Jack -- Comedian (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Bentley, Elizabeth (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Bera-Berh (Box 11, Folder 8 - 11)
    - Bergen, Edgar -- Ventriloquist (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Bergen, Polly -- Actress (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Bergman, Ingrid -- Alone and Heads (Box 11, Folder 15 - 17)
    - Bergman, Ingrid -- Groups (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Bergman, Ingrid -- With Rossellini, Lindstrom and New Baby (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Beri-Berm (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Bern (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Bernadette, Count Folke (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Bero-Berz (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Bes-Betz (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Betbeze, Yolande (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Betz, Pauline (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Bev-Bez (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Bevan, Jennifer (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Bevin, Ernest (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Bhackmer, Henry M. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Bidault, Georges (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Bil-Biq (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Bilbo, Theodore (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Bir-Bk (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Bl-Blk (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Black, A-Z (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Blaine, Vivian (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Blair, Janet (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Blake, A-Z (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Blanchard, A-Z (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Blanchard, Mari -- Actress (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Blandy, William H.P., Admiral (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Blankers-Koen, Fanny (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Blaz (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Ble-Bliz (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Blo-Bloz (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Blondell, Joan -- Actress (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Blu-Bn (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Blum, Leon (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Blyth, Ann (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Boa-Boe (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Bof-Bok (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Bogart, Humphrey -- Actor (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Bogeaus, Ben (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Bol-Bom (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Boland, Willie "Bill" -- Jockey (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Boles, John -- Actor (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Bolger, Ray -- Actor (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Bon-Bonz (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Bonnet, Henri (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Boo-Bov (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Boudreau, Lou (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Bow-Boz (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Bowen -- Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Bower -- Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Bower, Virginia -- 1949 Rose Queen (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Bowers -- Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Bowles, Chester (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Bowman, A-Z (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Bowman, Lee (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Bowron, Fletcher -- Mayor (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Boyd, A-Z (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Boyd, William (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Boyer, Charles -- Actor (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Boyington, Gregory (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Boyle -- Miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Bra (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Bracken, Eddie (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Braden -- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Bradford -- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Bradley, A-Z (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Bradley, Omar N., General (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Brady -- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Bragan, Bobby (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Branca, Ralph (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Brando, Marlon -- Actor (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Brandt -- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Brassard -- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Brasselle, Keefe -- And wife Norma (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Bratton -- Miscellaneous (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Brb-Brh (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Brent, George -- Actor (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Brewster, A-Z (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Bri-Briz (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Brian, David (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Brian, Mary -- Actress (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Bricker, John W., Governor (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Bridges, A-Z (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Bridges, Harry -- Labor Leader (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Bridges, Styles, Senator (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Briggs, A-Z (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Brinkman, Paul (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Briskin, Ted (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Brisson, Freddie (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Britton, Barbara -- Actress (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Bro-Brog (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Broderick -- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Broh-Brom (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Bromfield -- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Bron-Bros (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Brooks, A-Z (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Brophy (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Brot-Broz (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Brough (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Browder, Earl -- Communist (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Brown -- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Brown, A -- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Brown, Bobby -- Dr., Baseball (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Brown, C -- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Brown, Edmund G. (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Brown, H -- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Brown, J -- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Brown, James -- Mr. and Mrs., Actor (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Brown, Joe E. -- and Wife (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Brown, Johnny Mack -- Cowboy (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Brown, L -- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Brown, Marion --1980 Rose Queen (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Brown, P -- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Brown, R -- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Brown, S -- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Brown, T -- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Brown, Vanessa -- Actress (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Brown, W -- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Browne -- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Brownell, Herbert Jr. (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Browning -- Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Broz, Tito (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Bru-Bryz -- See Miscellaneous -- Bryan (Box 20, Folder 1 - 7)
    - Bruce, Virginia -- Actress (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Bryan, A-Z (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Bua-Buc (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Buchanan, A-Z (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Buck, Buckley -- A-Z (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Buckner, A-Z (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Bud (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Bue-Buk (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Buetel, Jack (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Buferd, Marilyn -- Miss America (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Bul-Buq (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Bunche, Ralph, Dr. (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Bura-Burl (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Burgman, Herbert J. -- Treason Charge (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Burke, A-Z (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Burke, Billie -- Actress (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Burm-Burz (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Burns, A-Z (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Burns, George -- And Grace Allen (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Burton, A-Z (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Bus-Busz (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Bush, A-Z (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - But-Bx (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Butler, A-Z (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Bya-Bz (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Byrd, Harry F., Senator (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Byrd, Richard E. (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Byrnes, James F. -- Alone and Groups of Two (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Byrnes, James F. -- Secretary of State -- Large Groups (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - C
    - C-Caj (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Cabot, Bruce (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Cagney, James -- Actor (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Cal-Calz (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Calhoun, Rory -- Actor (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Calhoun, Rory -- And Wife, Lita Baron (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Calvet, Corinne -- Actress (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Cam-Camz (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Cameron -- Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Cameron, Rod (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Camilli, Dolph -- Baseball (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Campbell, A-Z (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Canoya, Judy -- Actress (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Cantor, Eddie -- Actor (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Cantwell, John J. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Canzoneri, Tony -- Boxer (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Cap-Capz (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Cara-Cark (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Carey -- Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Carey, Macdonald -- Actor (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Carl-Carr (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Carlan, J.J. -- And wife -- Murder (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Carlise, Mary -- Actress (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Carlsen, Captain Henrik Kurt -- His Name Will Be Synonymous With Courage (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Carlson -- Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Caron, Leslie (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Carpenter, A-Z (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Carpenter, Garleton (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Carpenter, Norah (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Carrillo, Leo (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Carrington, Richard, Jr. (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Carroll and Carol -- A-Z (Box 24, Folder 10 - 12)
    - Carroll, John (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Cars-Carz (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Carson, Jack (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Carter -- Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Caruso -- Miscellaneous (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Casa-Casz (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Castel, Irene -- Dancer (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Caufield, Joan -- Actress (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Cerdan, Marcel -- Fighter (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Cg (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Chaa-Chaq (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Chadwick -- Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Chadwick, Florence (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Chaffee, Nancy -- Tennis (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Chambers, A-Z (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Chambers, Whitakers -- Spy Probe (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Champion, Gower -- and Marge (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Chandler, A-Z (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Chandler, A.B. "Happy" (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Chandler, Jeff (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Channing, Carol -- Stage Star (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Chao-Chan (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Chap (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Chaplin, Charley -- Actor (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Chapman, A-Z (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Chapman, Marguerite (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Chaq-Chaz (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Charisse, Cyd -- See Also Tony Martin (Box 26, Folder 7 - 9)
    - Charles, Ezzard (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Chatterton, Ruth -- Actress (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Chea-Chez (Box 26, Folder 12 - 16)
    - Chi-Chil (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Chim-Chq (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Ching, Cyrus -- And Mrs. (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Chr (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Christensen, A-Z (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Christian, A-Z (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Christian, Linda -- Actress (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Chs-Chuz (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Churchill, A-Z (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Churchill, Winston (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Cia-Ciz (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Cla-Clz (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Clark -- Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Clark, Bennet C., Senator (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Clark, Dane -- Actor (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Clark, Fred (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Clark, Georgia Neese (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Clark, Jimmy -- Golf (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Clark, Mark W., General (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Clark, Tom (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Clarke -- Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Clarke, Mae -- Actress (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Clay, Lucius D., General (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Clayton, Jan -- Actress (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Clooney, Rosemary -- Actress (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Coa-Coe (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Cobb, A-Z (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Coblentz -- Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Coburn, Charles (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Cochell, Earl (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Cochran, Cochrane, A-Z (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Cochran, Steve (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Cocke, Erle Jr. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Cod-Cof (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Coffee, A-Z (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Coffelt, Leslie (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Cog-Cok (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Cohen, Mickey -- Hollywood Gangster (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Cola-Coll (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Colbert, Claudette -- Actress (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Cole -- Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Coleman, A-Z (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Collazo, Oscar -- Mr. and Mrs. (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Collier, A-Z (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Collins, A-Z (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Collins, J. Lawton, General (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Collins, Joan (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Collyer, A-Z (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Colm-Colz (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Colman, Ronald -- Actor (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Colonna, Jerry -- Actor, Comedian (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Combs, Alice (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Como, Perry (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Con-Conz (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Conn, Billy -- Boxer (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Connally, Connolly, Connelly, A-Z (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Connally, Tom, Senator (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Connolly, Maureen -- Tennis (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Conte, Richard (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Coo-Coq (Box 31, Folder 2)